Guide to the Charles James Hendley Papers TAM.109
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Subject Files, 1914-1962
  - Amalgamated Textile Workers of America, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - American Federation of Labor (AFL) v. Congress of Industrial Organizatons (CIO), 1937-1938, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - AFL v. CIO: Communist Wreckers in American Labor, by Benjamin Stolberg, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - American Federation of Teachers: The American Teacher, 1932-1941 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Constitution, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Convention Materials (15th, 16th, 18th, 20th, 21st, 22nd, 23rd), 1931-1939 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Convention Materials (24th), 1940 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Correspondence, 1937-1941 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Dare the Teachers Do Their Public Duty? (Pre-WWII Program of Action), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Educational Defense Committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Executive Council Material, 1933-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Executive Council Material, 1939-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Finances, 1932-1941 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Printed Material - Pamphlets, Reprints, Bulletins, 1933-1938, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Roster of Locals, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - American Federation of Teachers: Various Reports, Statements and other Items, 1935-1942, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - American Labor Party, 1938-1945 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - American Labor Party, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - American Labor Party, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - American Labor Party, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - American Labor Party, 1951-1953, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - American Russian Institute, 1947, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - American Student Union, 1937-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting, 1941, 1948-1959, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: Earl Browder, 1941-1942, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: Harry Bridges and Longshoremen, 1942, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: Henry Steele Commager - Articles, 1947, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: House Committee on Un-American Activities / Dies Committee, 1939-1960 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: McCarthy, Joseph, 1952-1953, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: Smith Act, 1948-1960, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: Smith Act - Henry Winston, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Anti-Communism, Red Baiting: United Nations Probe, Oct 1952 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Anti-Nuclear Flyers, Pamphlets, Articles and Petitions, 1950-1962, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Semitism, 1938-1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Anti-War Material, 1929, 1937-1940, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Anti-War Material, 1948-1952, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bestor, Arthur E., Jr., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - "A Bill of Duties for the American People": Adopted by National Federation for Constitutional Liberties, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bland Bill (HR 5074), 1941 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Blank Forms, Stationery, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Books, Pamphlets and Other Documents: Lists, Announcements, 1942, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Brookwood Labor College and Arthur Calhoun, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Brownell, Herbert, Jr. v. United May Day Committee (Subversive Activities Control Board), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The Challenger: Comic (published by the Interfaith Committee of the Protestant Digest, Inc.), 1946 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Child Labor, 1924, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Childs, John L., 1936, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - City Housing Corporation: Sunnyside Gardens, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Civil Rights: Articles, Newsletters, Events, Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Civil Rights: Articles, Newsletters, Events, Correspondence, 1949-1960, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Classes, Seminars and School Announcements, 1930-1961, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Committee to Preserve Tenure, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Commonwealth College, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Communist Control Act of 1954 (Includes Letter from Hubert Humphrey) (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Communist Party, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Communist Party, 1958-1961, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Communist Party: The New Masses, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Communist Party: Section Committee Meetings and Related Material, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Compulsory Military Service, 1940, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Cooperative College for Social Reconstruction (New College), 1937 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Curriculum and Teaching Materials, 1923-1938 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Curriculum and Teaching Materials, 1941-1948 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Curriculum and Teaching Materials, 1950-1954, 1961, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Davis, Jerome, 1936, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dewey, John: The Crisis in Education and Why I Am a Member of the Teachers Union, 1933, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dodd, Bella: My Testimony to the Faith, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Downtown Community School, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Education: General, 1925, 1939-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Education: General, 1953-1960, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Education during Wartime, 1939 - Apr 1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Education during Wartime, May 1942 - 1943 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Education during Wartime, 1944-1946, 1950, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Education in New York State: Preliminary Annual Report, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Educational Organizations and Associations: Various, 1939-1953, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Eight Hour Work-Day Conference, 1917-1919 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Eight Hour Work-Day Conference, [1917-1919] (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Eight Hour Work-Day Conference: Delegate Credentials, 1918-1919 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Election Materials: Various, 1933-1937, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ethical Culture Schools, 1943-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1934-1946 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1947-1950, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Bills, 1939, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Separation of Church and State Issue, 1939-1945 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Federal Aid to Education: Separation of Church and State Issue, 1947-1948, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Five Cent Fare Committee, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - The Flivver King: Upton Sinclair novel, First Edition, Published by the United Auto Workers, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Floyd, William, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley: News Clippings and Campaign Materials, 1952-1957 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Fordism by Carl Raushenbush (League for Industrial Democracy), 1937 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Foundaton of Catholics for Human Brotherhood (Union Donations), 1945-1946 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Hawaii: Statehood, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - High School Teachers Association, [1929], 1933-1955 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - High School Teachers Association: Boycott of Unpaid Extracurricular Activities, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Hobbs Concentration Camp Bill, 1941, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Horace Wiliams Philosophical Society, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Howard University Contract with UPN-CIO for Teaching Staff, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Intolerance at Gompers Vocational High School (Timothy F. Murray), 1940 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Is Hitler Dead? and Best Anti-Nazi Humor, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science, 1946-1953, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Joint Committee of Teachers' Organizations, 1933-1939, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1942-1957, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Knickerbocker (William E.) Case, 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Labor Film Service, Inc., 1920, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Labor Is on the March, A Play (Incomplete, with Handwritten Notes), undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Labor Issues: Various, 1932-1959, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln School of Teachers College, Columbia University, 1926, 1929, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Literacy Test (New York State), undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Little Red School House, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Marzani, Carl, [1950] (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Methodist Federation for Social Service, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Milk Prices and the Penny Milk Program, 1941, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc., 1945-1947, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - National Defense (Pre WW-II, Teachers' Point of View), 1940, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - National Education Association, 1944-1945, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Education Association: Various Printed Materials, 1934-1945 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - National Education Association: Various Printed Materials, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - National Education Association: Various Printed Materials, 1947-1960, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - New China through Her Children's Eyes, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - New York State Federation of Teachers Unions, 1937-1942, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - New York State's Equal Pay Law, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Educational Issues, 1930-1958 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Educational Issues, 1959-1961, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Political Issues, 1933-1961, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Union Issues, 1940-1959 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Various, 1929, 1949-1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Ober Law, [1948] (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - On Scabs by Jack London, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Outline of the New Deal Legislation of 1933-1934 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - The Paris Commune by Karl Marx: American Edition published by New York Labor News Company, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - People's Congress and Peace Exposition, Chicago, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pepper, Claude: An American Policy for Peace..., 1946 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Play Schools Association, 1945-1947 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Post-WWII Planning Conferences, 1943-1945 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Progressive Education, 1936, 1950-1955, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Progressive Party, 1948, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Public Education Association: Various Printed Materials, 1939-1957, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Publications: After the War, Jun 1943 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Association of Teachers of Social Studies of New York City - ATSS Bulletin, 1944-1945 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Publications: BSC News (Better Schools Committee of the Southeast Bronx), May 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Publications: Bread and Butter, Feb 27, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Publications: Bulletin of the Teachers Alliance, 1940-1943 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Publications: College Newsletter, 1938-1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Columbia University, Jan 1951, Feb 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Publications: The Disinherited Speak, Letters from Sharecroppers, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Dynamo (High School of Science Creative Writing Club), Jun 1943 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Publications: Economic Notes, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Father Knickerbocker's Stepchild, Summary of an Impartial Inquiry into the Status of Public Libraries and Librarians of Greater New York, [1938] (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Publications: Foreign Policy Reports - Bretton Woods Monetary Conference Plans and Achievements, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Publications: Fusion Society (Parody), undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Publications: Greater New York Bulletin of the Merchants' Association of New York, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Publications: High School Teachers Association Bulletin, 1928, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Publications: How One Race Judges Another for Physical Attractiveness, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Publications: In Fact, 1940-1950 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Publications: Joint Committee of Teachers Organizations - Bulletin, 1934-1947 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Publications: Letters to Dad (CIO), undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Publications: Mexican Labor News (CIO), 1943-1944 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Publications: National Citizens Commission for the Public Schools - Citizens and their Schools, 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Publications: National Citizens Council for Better Schools - Better Schools, 1957, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Publications: Negro High-School Graduates and Nongraduates, Relation of their Occupational Status to Certain School Experiences, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Publications: New University Thought (Autumn), 1962 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Publications: NY State Federaton of Labor - Proceedings, 71st Annual Convention and Bulletin, 1934, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Publications: New York Teachers Guild - The Bulletin and Guild Teachers, 1938, 1941, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Publications: News of Africa, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Publications: Newsletter of the Commission on Teacher Education of the American Council on Education, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Publications: Progressive Education Association, 1933-1944 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Publications: Propaganda Analysis (The Institute for Propaganda Analysis, Inc.), Sep 1, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Publications: Report on World Affairs, Johannes Steel, Sep 1947, Feb 1950 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Publications: Russian Language, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Publications: School Life, Sep 1953 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Publications: Social Justice, Sep 15, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Publications: Soviet Aggression: Myth or Reality, Corliss Lamont, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Publications: Teacher Salaries, 1947, 1948, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Publications: Toward Freedom, Nov 1954 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Publications: Trends and Tides, Jan 1948 - Mar 1948 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Publications: Union Teacher (The Federation of Teachers Unions, State of New York), 1938 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Publications: Why the British People Fight, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Quinn, May A., 1943, 1950, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Reading Retardation, Jan 1954 - May 1954 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Reading Retardation, Jun 1954 -1959, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Reform Our Study, Mao Tse Tung, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Rhodes School Controversy, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln: Controversy over Speech Permit (NYC), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel, 1952-1954 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Roster of Teachers in the Public Schools of Camden, NJ, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Schappes, Morris: Statements, Information Letters, Press, Flyers, 1941-1943, undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - School Financing: School Bond Issue Referendum (Nov 3, 1959) (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - School Financing: Various Publications and Documents, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - School Financing: Various Publications and Documents, 1940-1948 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - School Financing: Various Publications and Documents, 1951-1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - School for Democracy, 1942, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - School Relief Fund, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Segregation/Discrimination in Schools, 1945-1961, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Segregation/Discrimination in Schools: Harlem, 1948, 1959, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Separation of Church and State: "The Catholic Hierarchy's Challenge to American Institutions" - Manuscripts, Drafts, Notes, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Separation of Church and State: "The Catholic Hierarchy's Challenge to American Institutions" - Manuscripts, Drafts, Notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Separation of Church and State: "The Catholic Hierarchy's Challenge to American Institutions" - Manuscript, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Separation of Church and State: "Dictation of School Policies by the Catholic Hierarchy" - Manuscript, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Separation of Church and State: School Prayer, Released Time and Other Education Issues, 1947-1952, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Shubert, Sara C., Agnes Doe and Cecelia C. Pollack v. Board of Education of the City of New York (Permanent Substitutes), 1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Sobell, Martin: Articles, Statements, Flyers, Solicitations, Correspondence, 1956-1960, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Social Studies, 1940-1941, 1948, 1951-1958, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Social Studies: Attacks on Textbooks, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Socialism: Father Gassoniana by Daniel DeLeun, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Socialist Party, 1935-1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Socialist Party: New Jersey, 1917, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Solicitations and Advertisements, 1942-1961, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Song Lyrics: Various, 1938, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Spanish Civil War: Correspondence, Articles, Solicitation, 1936-1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Spanish Civil War: Refugee Relief - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1938-1948, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Spanish Civil War: Refugee Relief - Various Organizations, 1939-1945, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Spanish Civil War: Refugee Relief - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1944-1952, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Statements, Newsletters, Brochures, Minutes: Various Organizations, 1937-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Teacher Retirement/Pension System, 1929-1950, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1937, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Unemployed Teachers, 1930-1941, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - United Nations, 1942-1947 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Various Teacher Organizations: Federation of Women High School Teachers, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Various Teacher Organizations: Houston Teachers Association and Syracuse Teachers Association, 1939, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Various Teacher Organizations: San Mateo County Teachers Association, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals, 1937-1940, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Boston (AFT), 1942 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Buffalo (AFT), 1938-1941 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Chicago (AFT), 1937-1941 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Chicago (AFT) - Chicago Union Teacher, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Ohio - Akron, Cincinnati, Cleveland (AFT), 1937-1940, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Philadelphia (AFT) - The Philadelphia Teacher, 1937-1939 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals: Seattle (AFT), 1938 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Various Teacher Unions, State Level: Minnesota State Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1939, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals (AFT), 1937-1939 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Various Teacher Union Locals (ATF), 1940 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Various Teacher Unions, State Level: New Jersey Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1938-1944 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Various Teacher Unions, State Level: Wisconsin State Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1938, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Veblen College, [1937] (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Walden School, 1940, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Wallace, Henry A.: Presidential Campaign, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square College of Arts and Sciences: Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Why the CIO Opened the Food Store", 1948 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Woll, Matthew, [1940] (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Worker, 1946-1962, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Worker: Correspondence, 1951-1962, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Worker: Financial and Other Administrative Materials, including Meeting Minutes, 1952-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - The Worker: Hendley Appearances before Internal Security Committee of the US Senate (1952) and Grand Jury (1962) regarding The Worker, 1952, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - The Worker: May Day, 1953-1961 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Worker Education, 1925-1939, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - World War II Materials, 1942, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Youth: Various Issues, 1926, 1939-1947, 1960, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Zorach, Tessim and Esta Gluck v. Andrew G. Clausen et al. (Supreme Court of the State of New York): Brief, [1951] (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1913-1959
  This series contains fifty black and white photographs, many of which are portraits of Hendley. The earliest is a 1913 photograph of Hendley and a group of students at a school in Monroe, North Carolina where he was a faculty member. Approximately twenty additional portraits depict Hendley throughout his life. A variety of Teachers Union events are also documented, including an Educational Conference, a 25th Anniversary gathering and a May Day Parade.
  - Hendley: Portrait, 1913 (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 1)
  - Hendley: Portraits, 1940s (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 2)
  - Hendley: Portraits, 1950s (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 3)
  - Hendley: Portraits, undated (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Union: 23rd Annual Educational Conference, 1959 (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 6)
  - Teachers Union: 25th Anniversary, Jun 1941 (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Union: May Day Parade, 1937 (Box Tamiment Shared A006, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified Parade (Oversize), [1940s] (Box Tamiment Shared OS008, Folder 1)